<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Justas Dauparas</title>
    <link>https://dauparas.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Justas Dauparas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 Justas Dauparas</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 06:44:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dauparas.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn it yourself - online resources</title>
      <link>https://dauparas.github.io/post/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 06:44:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dauparas.github.io/post/learning/</guid>
      <description>This is a short list of books and lectures with links for myself and anyone else who might find them useful. A book is worth a thousand arXiv papers!
Machine Learning Books  Pattern Recognition and Machine Learning by Christopher M. Bishop, Information Theory, Inference, and Learning Algorithms by David J.C. MacKay, videos, Machine Learning: A Probabilistic Perspective by Kevin P. Murphy, Bayesian Reasoning and Machine Learning by David Barber, Deep Learning by Ian Goodfellow, Yoshua Bengio, and Aaron Courville, The Elements of Statistical Learning by Trevor Hastie, Robert Tibshirani, and Jerome Friedman, All of Statistics A Concise Course in Statistical Inference by Larry Wasserman, Reinforcement learning: An introduction by Richard S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Normalizing Flows</title>
      <link>https://dauparas.github.io/post/normalizing_flows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 06:44:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dauparas.github.io/post/normalizing_flows/</guid>
      <description>In progress&amp;hellip;
Learn about normalizing flows  Review paper: Normalizing Flows for Probabilistic Modeling and Inference, Papamakarios, Nalisnick et al. Review paper: Normalizing Flows: An Introduction and Review of Current Methods, Kobyzev et al. Video lecture: Flow Models &amp;ndash; CS294-158-SP20 Deep Unsupervised Learning Video lecture: Invertible Models and Normalizing Flows, Laurent Dinh, ICLR 2020 Video lecture: Tutorial on normalizing flows, Eric Jang, ICML 2019 Blog: Flow-based Deep Generative Models, Lilian Weng Blog: Normalizing Flows Tutorial, Eric Jang  Definitions</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>